Guide to the Reuben A. Holden, Secretary of Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- University Secretary: General Correspondence and Subject File, 1901-1972 1953-1971; Series II
  - Benjamin, Judah P., 1945 (Box 47, Folder 264)
  - Berkeley, Bishop, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 265)
  - Berkeley Divinity School, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 266)
  - Betsy Ross Nursery School, 1953-1955, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 267-268)
  - Bibliography, 1955-1965, 1968-1969 (Box 47, Folder 269-270)
  - Bibliography reports, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 271)
  - Bicentennial: programs, invitations, 1901 (Box 47, Folder 272)
  - Bingham Oceanographic Laboratory, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 273)
  - Biology Department, 1966-1971 (Box 47, Folder 274)
  - Black Panthers, 1970 (Box 48, Folder 275)
  - Black Student Alliance, 1968-1970 (Box 48, Folder 276)
  - Blair, Edwin Foster, 1970-1971 (Box 48, Folder 277-278)
  - Blood Drive, 1969-1970 (Box 48, Folder 280)
  - Blue Cross, 1966-1970 (Box 48, Folder 281-283)
  - Blue Meeting House, 1969-1970 (Box 48, Folder 284)
  - Boating at Yale, 1903 (Box 48, Folder 285)
  - Books, 1967-1971 (Box 49, Folder 286-287)
  - Botany Department, 1956-1959 (Box 49, Folder 288)
  - Bowl, Yale: description and history, 1914-1964 (Box 49, Folder 289)
  - Boy Scouts of America, Quinnipiac Council of, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 290)
  - Branford First Congregational Church, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 291)
  - Brewster, President Kingman, Jr, and Secretary Holden letters, 1968-1970 (Box 49, Folder 291A)
  - Budget Office, 1968-1970 (Box 49, Folder 293-294)
  - Budget, Secretary's Office, 1925-1973 (Box 49, Folder 295)
  - Buildings and Grounds
    - 1953-1960 (Box 49, Folder 296)
    - 1956-1960 (Box 49, Folder 297)
    - 1957-1963 (Box 49, Folder 298-299)
    - 1965-1971 (Box 50, Folder 300-301)
  - Bulletin, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 302)
  - Bursar's Office, 1969-1971 (Box 50, Folder 303)
  - Business Manager, 1953-1971 (Box 50, Folder 304-307)
  - By-laws, 1963-1969 (Box 50, Folder 308)
  - C-general
    - 1953-1958 (Box 50, Folder 309)
    - 1954-1966 (Box 50, Folder 310-311)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 51, Folder 312-314)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 51, Folder 315)
  - Calender, University, 1954-1970 (Box 52, Folder 316-320)
  - California regional meetings, 1955 (Box 52, Folder 321)
  - Cambridge University, American Friends of, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 322)
  - Camp, Walter Memorial, 1926 (Box 52, Folder 323)
  - Campus police, 1959-1961 (Box 52, Folder 324)
  - Capital Requirements and Budgets Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 52, Folder 325)
  - Capital Resources Committee, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 326)
  - Carillonneurs, 1968-1971 (Box 52, Folder 327)
  - Carroll, Richard C., Associate Secretary, 1970-1971 (Box 52, Folder 328)
  - Catalogues, 1967-1968 (Box 53, Folder 329)
  - Center Church, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 330)
  - Center for Visitors Abroad, 1964-1968 (Box 53, Folder 331)
  - Certificates of Graduation, requests for, 1962-1969 (Box 53, Folder 332)
  - Challenge, 1959-1962 (Box 53, Folder 333-334)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1965-1971 (Box 53, Folder 335-337)
  - Chaplaincy, 1957-1958 (Box 54, Folder 338)
  - Chaplain's Office, 1967-1971 (Box 54, Folder 339)
  - Charities Drive, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 340)
  - Chemistry Department, 1956-1970 (Box 54, Folder 341-342)
  - Chicago Festival of Arts, 1956 (Box 54, Folder 343)
  - Child Study Center, 1970-1971 (Box 54, Folder 344)
  - Child's Memorial Fund By-laws (Jane Coffin), 1938 (Box 54, Folder 345)
  - Choate School, 1967-1968 (Box 54, Folder 346)
  - Choir gowns, 1942 (Box 54, Folder 347)
  - Chubb Fellows, 1967-1971 (Box 54, Folder 348)
  - Church of Christ, 1951-1965 (Box 54, Folder 349-350)
  - Church of Christ Bicentennial, 1957-1958 (Box 54, Folder 351)
  - Cincinnati trip, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 352)
  - City planning, 1969-1970 (Box 54, Folder 353)
  - Civil Defense, 1955-1969 (Box 55, Folder 354-357)
  - Civil War Memorial, 1928-1940 (Box 55, Folder 358)
  - Civil War, original lists, 1949 (Box 55, Folder 359)
  - Civilian aid, 1967-1968 (Box 55, Folder 360)
  - Clapp, Thomas, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 361)
  - Class Day, 1966, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 362-363)
  - Class Gift Fund, 1953-1963 (Box 56, Folder 364)
  - Class Officers Association, 1953-1965 (Box 56, Folder 365-368)
  - Class Reunion Bureau, 1952-1956 (Box 56, Folder 369)
  - Class Reunion Bureau, 1961-1970 (Box 56, Folder 370-374)
  - Classes, 1954-1972 (Box 57, Folder 375-381)
  - Classics Department, 1959-1970 (Box 57, Folder 382-383)
  - Clerical Bureau, 1967-1971 (Box 57, Folder 384)
  - Cleveland regional meeting, 1954 (Box 57, Folder 385)
  - Clippings, 1969-1971 (Box 57, Folder 386)
  - Co-education, 1965-1971 (Box 58, Folder 387-388)
  - Coffin, Charles A. Memorial Fund, 1967-1969 (Box 58, Folder 389)
  - Coffin, William Sloan, Jr., 1967-1968 (Box 58, Folder 390)
  - College Fellowships, 1955-1963 (Box 58, Folder 391-392)
  - Colleges: residential, 1952-1971 (Box 59, Folder 393-396)
  - Colleges and schools, other
    - 1954-1956 (Box 59, Folder 397)
    - 1955-1960 (Box 59, Folder 398-399)
    - 1961-1969 (Box 60, Folder 400-406)
    - 1969-1971 (Box 61, Folder 407-408)
  - Columbia University (Box 61, Folder 409)
  - Commencement, 1970-1971 (Box 61, Folder 410-411)
  - Commencement at other colleges, 1955 (Box 61, Folder 412)
  - Commencement polices, 1966-1967 (Box 61, Folder 413)
  - Commencement week Programs: Woolsey Hall platform plans, 1905-1942 (Box 61, Folder 414)
  - Committee on the Whole, 1968-1971 (Box 61, Folder 415)
  - Committee on Capital Requirements and Budgets, 1967-1968 (Box 61, Folder 416)
  - Community Affairs Committee, 1969-1971 (Box 62, Folder 417)
  - Community Charities Drive, 1952-1955 (Box 62, Folder 418)
  - Community Council of Greater New Haven, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 419)
  - Community Health Care Center, 1967-1971 (Box 62, Folder 420-425)
  - Computer Center, 1967-1969 (Box 63, Folder 426)
  - Computer Office, 1965-1970 (Box 63, Folder 427)
  - Conferences, 1956-1968 (Box 63, Folder 428-434)
  - Conferences, 1968-1971 (Box 64, Folder 435-436)
  - Conferences, summer
    - 1956-1957 (Box 64, Folder 437-438)
    - 1960-1962 (Box 64, Folder 439-441)
  - Congregational Christian Churches, 1953-1954 (Box 64, Folder 442)
  - Connecticut Coalition for a Responsible Congress, undated (Box 64, Folder 443)
  - Connecticut Conference of Independent Colleges, 1968-1970 (Box 65, Folder 444-445)
  - Connecticut Hall: guest suites, 1954-1956 (Box 65, Folder 446)
  - Connecticut Hall: guest suites and faculty room, 1967 (Box 65, Folder 447)
  - Connecticut Hall: reservations, 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 448)
  - Connecticut Junior Science and Humanities Symposium, 1963-1964 (Box 65, Folder 449)
  - Connecticut printers, 1968 (Box 65, Folder 450)
  - Connecticut, State of, 1966-1971 (Box 65, Folder 451)
  - Coordinating Officer of Military, Navy and Air Affairs, 1953-1958 (Box 65, Folder 452)
  - Copy Center Report, undated (Box 65, Folder 453)
  - Corinthian Yacht Club, 1964-1965 (Box 65, Folder 454)
  - Corporation
    - 1908-1922 (Box 66, Folder 455)
    - 1955-1964 (Box 66, Folder 456-461)
    - 1964-1970 (Box 67, Folder 462-467)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 68, Folder 468-469)
    - By-laws, 1967-1968 (Box 68, Folder 470)
    - Candidates, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 471-472)
    - Committees, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 473)
  - Council of Masters, 1968-1971 (Box 68, Folder 474)
  - Country Day School: Headmasters' Association meeting, 1955 (Box 68, Folder 475)
  - Courses of study:, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 476)
  - Council University
    - 1964-1967 (Box 69, Folder 477-478)
    - 1966-1971 (Box 69, Folder 479-480)
  - Community Progress Incorporated, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 481)
  - Committee for the Restoration of Italian Art, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 482)
  - Currier and Ives Prints, information re:, 1939 (Box 69, Folder 484)
  - D-general
    - 1953-1959 (Box 69, Folder 485)
    - 1956-1969 (Box 69, Folder 486-488)
    - 1969-1971 (Box 70, Folder 489-490)
  - Dames, Yale, 1968-1969 (Box 70, Folder 491)
  - Davenport College, 1953-1971 (Box 70, Folder 492-495)
  - Deaths, student, 1959-1962 (Box 70, Folder 496)
  - Decal requests, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 497)
  - Dedications, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 498)
  - Degrees
    - 1941-1971 (Box 70, Folder 499)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 70, Folder 500-501)
    - Master of Arts Privation, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 502)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 70, Folder 503-504)
  - Della Corte, matteo bust, Naples, Italy, 1965 (Box 70, Folder 505)
  - Departments, 1957-1966 (Box 71, Folder 506-507)
  - DeVane Medal, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 508)
  - DeVane Memorial, 1965-1969 (Box 71, Folder 509)
  - Development Board, 1965-1970 (Box 71, Folder 510-513)
  - Development brochures, 1960-1961 (Box 72, Folder 514-515)
  - Development Committee
    - 1957-1962 (Box 72, Folder 516-517)
    - 1959-1963 (Box 72, Folder 518)
    - 1964-1966 (Box 73, Folder 519)
  - Development Office
    - 1953-1965 (Box 73, Folder 520-524)
    - 1964-1969 (Box 73, Folder 525-529)
    - 1969-1971 (Box 74, Folder 530-531)
    - Dilieto, Biagio testimonial, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 532)
  - Dining Halls
    - 1923 (Box 74, Folder 533)
    - 1960-1963 (Box 74, Folder 534-535)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 74, Folder 536)
    - 1966-1969 (Box 74, Folder 537)
    - 1968-1970 (Box 74, Folder 538-539)
  - Diplomas
    - 1936-1958 (Box 74, Folder 540)
    - 1945-1966 (Box 74, Folder 541)
    - Harry B. Dorr, 1953-1961 (Box 74, Folder 542)
    - 1958-1968 (Box 74, Folder 543)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 74, Folder 544)
    - Harry B. Dorr, 1968 (Box 74, Folder 545)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 75, Folder 546)
    - 1968-1971 (Box 75, Folder 547)
  - Directory, 1968-1971 (Box 75, Folder 548)
  - Discipline, Report of the President's Committee, undated (Box 75, Folder 549)
  - Distinguished Teacher Awards on Parents Day, 1970-1971 (Box 75, Folder 550)
  - Divinity School
    - 1953-1953 (Box 75, Folder 551)
    - 1963-1965 (Box 75, Folder 552)
    - 1965-1971 (Box 76, Folder 553-556)
  - Drama School, 1954-1971 (Box 76, Folder 557-560)
  - Dramatic Association, 1910-1930 (Box 76, Folder 561)
  - Duro-Europas, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 562)
  - Dwight Chapel east window, 1960-1961 (Box 77, Folder 563)
  - Dwight Hall
    - 1953-1968 (Box 77, Folder 564-572)
    - 1968-1971 (Box 78, Folder 573-574)
  - Dwight Chapel dedication, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 575)
  - E-general
    - 1953-1958 (Box 78, Folder 576)
    - 1962-1971 (Box 78, Folder 577-581)
  - Economic Growth Center, 1968 (Box 78, Folder 582)
  - Economics Department
    - 1955-1957 (Box 78, Folder 583)
    - 1955-1964 (Box 78, Folder 584)
    - 1966-1971 (Box 78, Folder 585-586)
  - Education Board, 1963-1964 (Box 79, Folder 587)
  - Education Center, Ecumenical, 1968-1970 (Box 79, Folder 588)
  - Education: general, 1953-1958 (Box 79, Folder 589)
  - Education Improvement Center, 1970 (Box 79, Folder 590)
  - Education, State Department of, 1950-1963, 1965 (Box 79, Folder 591-592)
  - Education Corporation, 1968-1970 (Box 79, Folder 593-594)
  - Education Policy Committee, 1966-1971 (Box 79, Folder 595-596)
  - Educational Research Office, 1960-1968 (Box 79, Folder 597)
  - Education research statistics, 1967 (Box 79, Folder 598)
  - Educational television, 1967 (Box 79, Folder 599)
  - Elizabethan Club, 1959-1965 (Box 79, Folder 600)
  - Elliott, Zo: "Long Long Trail A-Winding,", 1964-1966 (Box 79, Folder 600A)
  - Elmo, Saint, Committee on Foreign Students, 1964-1966 (Box 80, Folder 601-602)
  - Employee relations, 1967-1970 (Box 80, Folder 603)
  - Endowment, gift reports, 1965-1971 (Box 80, Folder 604)
  - Endowment Management and Research Corporation
    - 1967-1968 (Box 80, Folder 605-606)
    - 1969 (Box 81, Folder 607-608)
    - 1971 (Box 81, Folder 609)
  - Engagement book, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 610)
  - Engineering School
    - 1921 (Box 81, Folder 611)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 81, Folder 612)
    - 1957-1960 (Box 81, Folder 613)
    - 1960-1965 (Box 82, Folder 614-617)
  - Engineers Conference, President's Committee, 1958 (Box 82, Folder 618)
  - English Department, 1955-1970 (Box 82, Folder 619-622)
  - Engrossers, for diplomas, 1960-1964 (Box 82, Folder 623)
  - "Enjoying New Haven", 1967 (Box 82, Folder 624)
  - "Enormous Room, The,", 1966-1968 (Box 82, Folder 625)
  - Enrolled students, 1953-1957 (Box 82, Folder 626-627)
  - Enrollment figures, 1966 (Box 82, Folder 628)
  - Enrollment and scholarship, 1953-1963 (Box 82, Folder 629-631)
  - Enrollment trends, 1959-1962 (Box 82, Folder 632)
  - Equipment, office, 1953-1957 (Box 82, Folder 633)
  - Expense account reports, 1953-1958 (Box 82, Folder 634)
  - F-general, 1953-1971 (Box 83, Folder 635-640)
  - "Facts about Yale", 1967-1968 (Box 83, Folder 641)
  - Faculty appointments and retirements, 1953-1958 (Box 83, Folder 642)
  - Faculty bulletin, 1963-1964 (Box 83, Folder 643)
  - Faculty Club
    - 1953-1957 (Box 83, Folder 644)
    - 1956-1966 (Box 83, Folder 645)
    - 1968 (Box 83, Folder 646)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 83, Folder 647)
  - Faculty Club history, 1921-1949 (Box 83, Folder 648)
  - Faculty deferments, 1956 (Box 84, Folder 649)
  - Faculty directory, 1955-1959 (Box 84, Folder 650)
  - Faculty handbook, 1969 (Box 84, Folder 651)
  - Faculty lists, 1953-1963, 1969 (Box 84, Folder 652-654)
  - Faculty policies, 19691 (Box 84, Folder 655)
  - Faculty salaries, 1940-1951 (Box 84, Folder 656)
  - Fair Labor Standards Act, 1968 (Box 84, Folder 657)
  - Federal aid to education, 1961 (Box 84, Folder 659)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation (forms), undated (Box 84, Folder 660)
  - Fellows of Colleges meetings, 1962 (Box 84, Folder 661)
  - Fellowships, 1969-1971 (Box 84, Folder 662)
  - Festival of Arts, New Haven, 1968 (Box 84, Folder 663)
  - Film Committee, 1955-1963 (Box 84, Folder 664)
  - Financial Aid Office, 1965-1970 (Box 84, Folder 665)
  - Five-Year B.A. Program: annual dinner guest list, undated (Box 84, Folder 666)
  - Flag, United States, use of, undated (Box 84, Folder 667)
  - Football captains, 1876-1962 (Box 84, Folder 668)
  - Foote School, 1968-1969 (Box 84, Folder 669)
  - Foreign alumni, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 671)
  - Foreign Nationals Office, 1953-1963 (Box 85, Folder 672-674)
  - Foreign Student Institute, 1959-1963 (Box 85, Folder 675-677)
  - Foreign Students, Inter-School Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 85, Folder 678)
  - Forestry School, 1953-1967 (Box 85, Folder 679-680)
  - Forestry School, 1968-1971 (Box 86, Folder 681-682)
  - Forestry School, booklets, "Second Half Century Growth,", undated (Box 86, Folder 683)
  - Fraternities, 1955-1961 (Box 86, Folder 685)
  - French Department, 1954-1966,1969 (Box 86, Folder 686-688)
  - Freshman Assembly
    - 1953-1961 (Box 86, Folder 689-694)
    - 1962-1964 (Box 87, Folder 695-697)
    - 1966-1970 (Box 87, Folder 698-700)
  - Freshman year, 1953-1964 (Box 87, Folder 701-702)
  - Funerals, 1967-1971 (Box 87, Folder 703-706)
  - G-general
    - 1953-1960 (Box 88, Folder 707)
    - 1955-1971 (Box 88, Folder 708-712)
  - General Assembly of Connecticut: support given to Yale, 1965 (Box 88, Folder 713)
  - Geology Department, 1953-1971 (Box 88, Folder 714-715)
  - German Department, 1953-1971 (Box 88, Folder 716-717)
  - German reading room, 1962-1966 (Box 88, Folder 718)
  - Gibbs, Josiah Willard, 1871-1903 (Box 89, Folder 719)
  - Gibbs Society, 1969 (Box 89, Folder 722)
  - Gift Acknowledgements
    - 1960-1966 (Box 89, Folder 723-726)
    - 1966-1971 (Box 90, Folder 727-730)
  - Gifts, furniture, 1953-1960 (Box 90, Folder 731)
  - Gifts: money, 1953-1961 (Box 91, Folder 736)
  - Glee Club
    - 1935-1958 (Box 91, Folder 737)
    - 1954-1971 (Box 91, Folder 738-745)
  - Gordon Brown Prize, 1971 (Box 92, Folder 746)
  - Government, United States State Department, Department of Education, 1954-1966 (Box 92, Folder 747)
  - Grace-New Haven Community Hospital
    - 1953-1955 (Box 92, Folder 748)
    - 1954-1965 (Box 92, Folder 749-752)
  - Graduate Club, 1964-1971 (Box 92, Folder 753-754)
  - Graduate School, 1954-1971 (Box 93, Folder 755-763)
  - Grant and Contract Administration, 1969 (Box 93, Folder 764)
  - Graphic Arts Center, 1963-1964 (Box 93, Folder 766)
  - Griswold, Alfred Whitney, 1953-1960 (Box 93, Folder 767)
  - Griswold, Mary B., 1957 (Box 93, Folder 768)
  - Guests, accommodations for University, 1956-1958 (Box 94, Folder 769)
  - Guiding instructions, 1961 (Box 94, Folder 771)
  - Guiding and reception of visitors, 1964-1966 (Box 94, Folder 772)
  - Gymnasium, Payne Whitney, 1969-1971 (Box 94, Folder 773)
  - Gymnasium, Payne Whitney and Ray Tomkins House, 1932-94 (Box 94, Folder 773A)
  - H-General
    - 1953-1956 (Box 94, Folder 774)
    - 1954-1956 (Box 94, Folder 775)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 94, Folder 776)
    - 1968-1971 (Box 95, Folder 777-779)
  - Harrow School: Halsted B. Vander, 1970 (Box 95, Folder 781)
  - Harvard University, 1953-1968 (Box 95, Folder 782-783)
  - Hathaway, John S.: reception, undated (Box 95, Folder 784)
  - Headmaster candidates, 1952-1967 (Box 95, Folder 786)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, 1966 (Box 96, Folder 787)
  - Health, University, 1965-1971 (Box 96, Folder 788-789)
  - Helen Hadley Hall, 1960-1969 (Box 96, Folder 790-792)
  - Hendel, Charles D., 1959 (Box 96, Folder 793)
  - Heraldry, 1967 (Box 96, Folder 794)
  - Hewitt Quadrangle, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 795)
  - High schools, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 796)
  - Historical Landmarks, National, 1966 (Box 96, Folder 798)
  - Histories of Yale University, 1950-1966 (Box 96, Folder 799)
  - History Department, 1954-1970 (Box 97, Folder 800-803)
  - History of Yale at War, 1943 (Box 97, Folder 804)
  - Holden, Reuben A.: portrait unveiling, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 806)
  - Honor rolls (Box 97, Folder 807A)
  - Hopkins Grammer School
    - 1964-1966 (Box 97, Folder 808-809)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 98, Folder 810-811)
  - Housing Bureau
    - 1953-1959 (Box 98, Folder 812)
    - 1961-1970 (Box 98, Folder 813-815)
  - Howland Memorial Prize, 1965-1966 (Box 98, Folder 816)
  - Hoyt Fellowship, 1965-1969 (Box 98, Folder 817)
  - I general, 1953-1955 (Box 98, Folder 818-819)
  - Inauguration, James R. Angell, 1921 (Box 98, Folder 820)
  - Inauguration, Arthur T. Hadley, 1899 (Box 98, Folder 821)
  - Inaugural delegates, 1969-1970 (Box 98, Folder 822)
  - Independent colleges within the Yale Community, undated (Box 98, Folder 823)
  - Industrial Administration Department, 1950-1963, 1965-1967 (Box 99, Folder 825-826)
  - Information Office, 1957-1963, 1967-1970 (Box 99, Folder 827-828)
  - Inquiries for jobs at Yale and elsewhere, 1953-1959 (Box 99, Folder 829-830)
  - Institute of Far Eastern Languages
    - 1953-1959 (Box 99, Folder 831-832)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 99, Folder 833)
    - 1960-1962 (Box 100, Folder 834-836)
    - 1962 (Box 100, Folder 837)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 100, Folder 838)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 100, Folder 839)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 100, Folder 840)
  - Institute of Human Rights, undated (Box 100, Folder 841)
  - Institute of Social Science, 1968-1969 (Box 100, Folder 842)
  - Institutional Policies Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 100, Folder 843)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council, 1967-1968 (Box 100, Folder 844)
  - International Association of Universities, 1966-1968 (Box 100, Folder 845)
  - International Exchange Programs, 1963-1967 (Box 101, Folder 846-848)
  - International Office
    - 1963-1966 (Box 101, Folder 849-852)
    - 1966-1970 (Box 102, Folder 853-858)
  - International Student Center
    - 1957-1962 (Box 102, Folder 859-860)
    - 1961-1971 (Box 103, Folder 861-867)
  - International Student Programs and Exchange, 1960-1963 (Box 103, Folder 868)
  - International Understanding, Business Council for, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 869)
  - International Visitor Program, 1967 (Box 103, Folder 870)
  - Introduction, notes of, 1959-1968 (Box 103, Folder 871-873)
  - Invitations, 1969-1971 (Box 104, Folder 874-876)
  - J-general, 1953-1971 (Box 104, Folder 877-879)
  - Jarvis Collection: Early Italian paintings, undated (Box 104, Folder 879A)
  - Johns Hopkins University, 1967 (Box 104, Folder 880)
  - Johnson, President Andrew, 1944 (Box 104, Folder 880A)
  - Junior Science and Humanities Symposium, 1969 (Box 104, Folder 881)
  - K-general, 1953-1971 (Box 104, Folder 882-885)
  - Kendall, Sargeant: pastel portraits, 1945 (Box 104, Folder 885A)
  - Klein-Beinecke portraits: correspondence, 1965 (Box 104, Folder 886)
  - L-general, 1958-1971 (Box 105, Folder 887-890)
  - Language Laboratory, 1964 (Box 105, Folder 891)
  - Law School, 1954-1965 (Box 105, Folder 892-895)
  - Law School, 1965-1971 (Box 106, Folder 896-899)
  - League of Women Voters, 1969 (Box 106, Folder 900-902)
  - Lee case, 1961-1962 (Box 106, Folder 903)
    General note
    [restricted material moved to series IV]
  - Lectures
    - Bromley, 1965-1971 (Box 106, Folder 904)
    - Chubb Fellowship, 1966 (Box 106, Folder 905)
    - Dante Alighieri: Cultural Center, 1969 (Box 106, Folder 906)
    - General, 1966-1970 (Box 106, Folder 907-910)
    - Gooch, 1968-1969 (Box 106, Folder 911)
    - Harvard, 1968-1971 (Box 106, Folder 912)
    - Hoyt, 1966-1971 (Box 106, Folder 913)
    - Hume, 1966-1971 (Box 107, Folder 914)
    - Lamont, 1966-1970 (Box 107, Folder 915)
    - Science and the Citizen, 1966 (Box 107, Folder 916)
    - Silliman
      - 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 917)
      - 1967-1969 (Box 107, Folder 918)
      - 1967-1971 (Box 107, Folder 919-920)
    - Spaulding, 1968 (Box 107, Folder 921)
    - Terry
      - 1964-1970 (Box 107, Folder 922-924)
      - 1968-1971 (Box 107, Folder 925)
      - 1966-1971 (Box 107, Folder 926)
    - Trumbull, 1966-1971 (Box 107, Folder 927-929)
    - University, 1966-1969 (Box 108, Folder 930)
    - Woodward, 1966-1971 (Box 108, Folder 931-935)
  - Letters by President Brewster and Secretary Holden
    See: box 49, folder 291A
  - Library
    - 1944-1960 (Box 108, Folder 937)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 108, Folder 938)
    - 1963-1969 (Box 109, Folder 939-942)
  - Library Associates, 1951 (Box 109, Folder 943)
  - Library memorabilia, 1955-1960 (Box 109, Folder 944)
  - Library and Museums Committee, 1960-1965 (Box 109, Folder 945-946)
  - Library, Sterling Memorial, 1969-1971 (Box 109, Folder 948)
  - Linguistics Department, 1957-1967 (Box 109, Folder 949)
  - Literary Magazine, Yale, 1958 (Box 109, Folder 949A)
  - Lohman, Carl A., 1957 (Box 109, Folder 950)
  - Lynd, Staughton, 1967 (Box 109, Folder 952)
  - M-general
    - 1953-1963 (Box 110, Folder 952A-953)
    - 1967-1971 (Box 110, Folder 954-957)
  - Machu Picchu and Hiram Bingham, 1968 (Box 110, Folder 957A)
  - Madras, India, 1969 (Box 110, Folder 958)
  - Management operations, 1968 (Box 110, Folder 959)
  - Married student housing, 1960-1963 (Box 110, Folder 960)
  - Master of Arts Teaching Program, 1954-1963 (Box 110, Folder 961)
  - Master of Arts Teaching Program, 1964-1967,1969 (Box 111, Folder 962-963)
  - Masters, Council of, 1953-1958 (Box 111, Folder 963A)
  - Mathematics Department, 1969 (Box 111, Folder 964)
  - Medical School
    - 1911-1960 (Box 111, Folder 965)
    - 1953-1965 (Box 111, Folder 966-968)
    - 1964-1968 (Box 111, Folder 969-972)
    - 1969-1971 (Box 112, Folder 973-974)
  - Merriwell, Frank, 1941 (Box 112, Folder 974A)
  - Military intelligence, 1958-1959 (Box 112, Folder 975)
  - Military obligations, 1955-1956 (Box 112, Folder 976)
  - Military Science Department
    - 1955-1962 (Box 112, Folder 977-978)
    - 1960-1962 (Box 112, Folder 979)
    - 1961-1963 (Box 112, Folder 980)
    - 1963-1968 (Box 113, Folder 981-985)
  - Military Studies Program, 1962 (Box 113, Folder 986)
  - Molecular Biology and Biophysics, 1963-1965 (Box 113, Folder 987)
  - "Morse, Samuel F.B., 1761-1826" [article], 1967 (Box 113, Folder 987A)
  - Mory's Association
    - 1953-1968 (Box 113, Folder 988-990)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 113, Folder 991)
  - Munich, America week in, 1961 (Box 114, Folder 992)
  - Music School
    - 1954-1960 (Box 114, Folder 993)